<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recipes on Cambron.cc</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/</link><description>Recent content in Recipes on Cambron.cc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cambron.cc/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chicken Biriyani - Instant Pot</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2023-03-11-chicken-biriyani/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2023-03-11-chicken-biriyani/</guid><description>Ingredients Marinade 180 g Plain Yogurt
1 tbsp Garam Masala
1 tbsp Red Chili Powder (from an Indian grocer, use Hot for more kick, Kashmiri for mild)
1/2 tsp Tumeric Powder
1 tbsp Ginger - Grated
3 cloves Garlic - Pressed
8 grams - Fresh Mint - chopped
8 grams - Fresh Cilantro - chopped</description></item><item><title>Raclette</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2022-12-23-raclette/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2022-12-23-raclette/</guid><description>At its simplest Raclette is a soft alpine cheese that is traditionally served melted, over boiled potatoes.
However, the practice of using a tabletop grill to melt Raclette cheese and prepare a variety of other foods is a popular winter past-time across the German speaking world.
As with many other Americans however, the world of Raclette is still somewhat foreign. The &amp;ldquo;pack in the box&amp;rdquo; instructions that accompany American Raclette grills sell short this lovely way of grazing over melted cheese and meats.</description></item><item><title>Jim Lahey's No Knead Bread ala Cambron</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2021-02-20-jim-laheys-no-knead-bread-ala-cambron/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2021-02-20-jim-laheys-no-knead-bread-ala-cambron/</guid><description>Baking bread was more or less an accident. My father bakes bread, my friends bake bread, and for the last few years I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to eat low carb. Somehow I thought I&amp;rsquo;d avoid the bug&amp;hellip;
This recipe is probably the most popular white bread recipe on the internet, and there are already a LOT of variations on this recipe. My suggestions are limited, and already available on various comment threads.</description></item><item><title>Rye Bread (Roggenmischbrot 2:1)</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2021-02-07-rye-bread-roggenmischbrot-21/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2021-02-07-rye-bread-roggenmischbrot-21/</guid><description>The finished bread after a day of resting. (Attempt 1)
One of things that I miss the most about living in Germany is the incredible variety of breads that just aren&amp;rsquo;t available in the United States.
During Covid-19, I&amp;rsquo;ve been making weekly loaves of Jim Lahey&amp;rsquo;s No Knead bread, and thought my next bread should be one that I am unable to find in the United States.
After doing a little hunting on the internet I stumbled across Plötzblog: an incredible bread baking site with many of the German bread recipes I missed with recipes to bake at home.</description></item><item><title>Australian Sausage Rolls</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2020-11-25-australian-sausage-rolls/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2020-11-25-australian-sausage-rolls/</guid><description>Ingredients Meat 500g Ground Beef
500g Ground Pork
Produce 3 Cloves Garlic
1 Carrot
1 Celery Stalk
1 Medium Brown Onion
Dry Spices Seasoning Mix 1 Tbsp Nutmeg
1 Tbsp Sage
1 Tbsp Onion Powder
1 Tbsp Paprika (Sweet)
1 Tbsp Thyme
For Mince Salt &amp;amp; Pepper
Bundle Fresh Parsley
For Garnish 1 Tbsp Fennel Seed
Additional Ingredients 1.5 Tbsp Tomato Paste
Worcestershire Sauce
.5 Cup Breadcrumbs
Cooking Oil
Ketchup</description></item><item><title>Punky German Beer Cheese (Obazda)</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2020-05-06-punky-german-beer-cheese-obazda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2020-05-06-punky-german-beer-cheese-obazda/</guid><description>One of my favorite parts of enjoying a German Biergarten in the summer is the onion covered cheese spread that goes on a crusty Bavarian pretzel.
Here is my recipe for Obazda, using readily available ingredients in the USA
Ingredients 250g Camembert (let ripen! the stinkier the better!)
20g (2 tbsp) Butter
100g (half a package) Philadelphia cream cheese (Frischkäse if available)
50g (half a small onion) finely chopped onion (cut in half to create rings)</description></item><item><title>Quick and Easy Hot Tomatillo Salsa</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2020-03-27-quick-and-easy-hot-tomatillo-salsa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2020-03-27-quick-and-easy-hot-tomatillo-salsa/</guid><description>Smoky spicy goodness
My attempt at making a tomatillo salsa with easily acquirable ingredients that is a consistent favorite!
Ingredients 16 Tomatillos - remove skins and rinse
5 Cloves Garlic
1 Jalapeño
5-6 dried red chilies or a spoonful of red chili powder (I actually like Indian red chili powder best, NOT chili powder from the grocery store, which includes additional spices)
Salt
spoonful of cumin
juice from 1/2 lime</description></item><item><title>REZEPT: Pfeffernüsse</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-24-rezept-pfeffernusse/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-24-rezept-pfeffernusse/</guid><description>The next recipe recipe I want to look at is for Pfeffernüsse&amp;hellip; This is a case where our recipe has drifted very far from the German interpretation, but they still remain a popular staple at Christmas time&amp;hellip; Oddly the recipe card I was given reads &amp;ldquo;Neusenfefferson&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; which I can only assume was a mistake. Google yields no results for Neusenfefferson.
American Recipe German Recipe (courtesy of Dr. Oetker) 1/2 lb (225g) Butter, creamed with 3 cup (360 g) Flour 1/2 tsp Vanilla 2 cups (30g) Ground Pecans 25g Candied Citron 250g Wheat Flour 1 1/2 tsp Baking Powder 160g Sugar Lemon Zest 1 pinch of Salt 1 Egg 1 pinch of Ginger 1 pinch of Cardamom 1 pinch of Cloves 1 pinch of Allspice 1 pinch of fresh ground white pepper 3 1/2 tbsp Milk 25g ground Almonds Mix ingredients well and shape into small balls the size of English walnuts.</description></item><item><title>Rezept: Springerle (Anise Cookies)</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-24-rezept-springerle-anise-cookies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-24-rezept-springerle-anise-cookies/</guid><description>Probably the most fascinating from a chemistry standpoint, Springerle come from the Swabian tradition of alkalized baking. Here I believe that our family recipe is actually MORE accurate than Dr. Oetker (essentially the German &amp;ldquo;Betty Crocker&amp;rdquo;), as Oetker recommends using their own branded &amp;ldquo;Backin&amp;rdquo; baking powder instead of Hirschhornsalz (Hartshorn, Ammonium Carbonate, Bakers Ammonium)
While obtaining Hartshorn used to be the most difficult part of making this recipe, it can now be easily obtained from Amazon.</description></item><item><title>Rezept: Spritzgebäck</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-24-rezept-spritzgeback/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-24-rezept-spritzgeback/</guid><description>Third up and most popular around Christmas at our house are Spritzgebäck&amp;hellip;. although they have always just been called &amp;ldquo;s-cookies&amp;rdquo; in our family.
American Recipe German Recipe (courtesy of Dr. Oetker) 2 1/2 cups (300g) Flour 1/2 tsp Salt 1 Cup (225g) Butter 3/4 Cup (150g) Sugar 1 Egg (or 3 Yolks) 3/4 tsp Almond Extract 500g (4.2 cups) Flour 1 pinch of Salt 250g (1.</description></item><item><title>Rezept: Zimtsterne</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-23-rezept-zimtsterne/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-23-rezept-zimtsterne/</guid><description>Of particular interest to me, is the way in which immigrant foods, like Christmas cookies have changed to adapt to American tastes/American kitchens.
Having spent considerable time baking heirloom family cookie recipes in the kitchen at Christmas with my family. I thought it would be interesting to compare my family recipes with how they now exist in modern Germany.
My great aunt Alice was often considered the &amp;ldquo;master of these recipes&amp;rdquo; and helped translate some of them from German at sometime.</description></item><item><title>Cauliflower Crust Pizza</title><link>https://cambron.cc/.../</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/.../</guid><description>Ingredients 2 cups of finely ground Cauliflower Rice (from one head of Cauliflower) 1/4 cup parmesan cheese 1/4 cup cheddar or mozzarella cheese 1/4 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon basil 1/2 teaspoon oregano 1/2 teaspoon garlic powder 1/8 teaspoon red chili powder 2 tablespoon almond flour 1 egg Method Place a pizza stone in the oven. Preheat oven to 450 degrees.
On a cutting board, prepare a piece of parchment paper and spray it with avocado oil.</description></item></channel></rss>