<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Creative Commons on Cambron.cc</title><link>https://cambron.cc/categories/creative-commons/</link><description>Recent content in Creative Commons on Cambron.cc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cambron.cc/categories/creative-commons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Open / Creative Commons / Free Resources</title><link>https://cambron.cc/teaching/digcom/resources/software/a-quick-note/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/teaching/digcom/resources/software/a-quick-note/</guid><description>Open / Creative Commons / Free Resources Below are curated resources for finding images/graphics that are licensed in a way that allows for remix/reuse.
Photographic Images Openverse Pixabay Nappy Images of Empowerment Europeana EDU Images StockSnap Pexels Textures TextureLabs Photoshop Brushes Kyle’s Brushes Brusheezy Clip Art / Vector Art / Line Drawings Open Clip Art Drawkit Undraw Lukaz Adams Open Peeps Humaaans Fonts DaFont Google Fonts Font Fabric – Free Fonts Font Squirrel 1001 Fonts Icons Noun Project Flaticon Simple Icons Ionicons Animaticons Videos Mixkit Videezy Coverr Videvo Life of Vids Audio Freesound Bensound</description></item><item><title>Auf dem Weg! High School German</title><link>https://cambron.cc/teaching/pedagogy/2020-08-08-auf-dem-weg-high-school-german/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/teaching/pedagogy/2020-08-08-auf-dem-weg-high-school-german/</guid><description>A project that I have been stewing on for a long time is now being realized due to the passion of a dedicated group of High School teachers.
To check out the project on Rebus Community here</description></item><item><title>Creative Commons Certificate - Unit 1</title><link>https://cambron.cc/teaching/pedagogy/2020-01-20-creative-commons-certificate-unit-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/teaching/pedagogy/2020-01-20-creative-commons-certificate-unit-1/</guid><description>This week I&amp;rsquo;m beginning licensing through the Creative Commons and I wanted to use this blog post to collect my thoughts and ideas from the process.
Course Design and Apps While taking the course, probably the thing that struck me first was the way the course was structured, and the way course was designed, and the learning apps it utilizes. Here are a few that have been part of the course, that I am interested to learn more about.</description></item></channel></rss>