<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hobbies on Cambron.cc</title><link>https://cambron.cc/categories/hobbies/</link><description>Recent content in hobbies on Cambron.cc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cambron.cc/categories/hobbies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jim Lahey's No Knead Bread ala Cambron</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2021-02-20-jim-laheys-no-knead-bread-ala-cambron/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2021-02-20-jim-laheys-no-knead-bread-ala-cambron/</guid><description>Baking bread was more or less an accident. My father bakes bread, my friends bake bread, and for the last few years I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to eat low carb. Somehow I thought I&amp;rsquo;d avoid the bug&amp;hellip;
This recipe is probably the most popular white bread recipe on the internet, and there are already a LOT of variations on this recipe. My suggestions are limited, and already available on various comment threads.</description></item><item><title>Rye Bread (Roggenmischbrot 2:1)</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2021-02-07-rye-bread-roggenmischbrot-21/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2021-02-07-rye-bread-roggenmischbrot-21/</guid><description>The finished bread after a day of resting. (Attempt 1)
One of things that I miss the most about living in Germany is the incredible variety of breads that just aren&amp;rsquo;t available in the United States.
During Covid-19, I&amp;rsquo;ve been making weekly loaves of Jim Lahey&amp;rsquo;s No Knead bread, and thought my next bread should be one that I am unable to find in the United States.
After doing a little hunting on the internet I stumbled across Plötzblog: an incredible bread baking site with many of the German bread recipes I missed with recipes to bake at home.</description></item><item><title>Quick and Easy Hot Tomatillo Salsa</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2020-03-27-quick-and-easy-hot-tomatillo-salsa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2020-03-27-quick-and-easy-hot-tomatillo-salsa/</guid><description>Smoky spicy goodness
My attempt at making a tomatillo salsa with easily acquirable ingredients that is a consistent favorite!
Ingredients 16 Tomatillos - remove skins and rinse
5 Cloves Garlic
1 Jalapeño
5-6 dried red chilies or a spoonful of red chili powder (I actually like Indian red chili powder best, NOT chili powder from the grocery store, which includes additional spices)
Salt
spoonful of cumin
juice from 1/2 lime</description></item><item><title>Creative Commons Certificate - Unit 1</title><link>https://cambron.cc/teaching/pedagogy/2020-01-20-creative-commons-certificate-unit-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/teaching/pedagogy/2020-01-20-creative-commons-certificate-unit-1/</guid><description>This week I&amp;rsquo;m beginning licensing through the Creative Commons and I wanted to use this blog post to collect my thoughts and ideas from the process.
Course Design and Apps While taking the course, probably the thing that struck me first was the way the course was structured, and the way course was designed, and the learning apps it utilizes. Here are a few that have been part of the course, that I am interested to learn more about.</description></item><item><title>REZEPT: Pfeffernüsse</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-24-rezept-pfeffernusse/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-24-rezept-pfeffernusse/</guid><description>The next recipe recipe I want to look at is for Pfeffernüsse&amp;hellip; This is a case where our recipe has drifted very far from the German interpretation, but they still remain a popular staple at Christmas time&amp;hellip; Oddly the recipe card I was given reads &amp;ldquo;Neusenfefferson&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; which I can only assume was a mistake. Google yields no results for Neusenfefferson.
American Recipe German Recipe (courtesy of Dr. Oetker) 1/2 lb (225g) Butter, creamed with 3 cup (360 g) Flour 1/2 tsp Vanilla 2 cups (30g) Ground Pecans 25g Candied Citron 250g Wheat Flour 1 1/2 tsp Baking Powder 160g Sugar Lemon Zest 1 pinch of Salt 1 Egg 1 pinch of Ginger 1 pinch of Cardamom 1 pinch of Cloves 1 pinch of Allspice 1 pinch of fresh ground white pepper 3 1/2 tbsp Milk 25g ground Almonds Mix ingredients well and shape into small balls the size of English walnuts.</description></item><item><title>Rezept: Springerle (Anise Cookies)</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-24-rezept-springerle-anise-cookies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-24-rezept-springerle-anise-cookies/</guid><description>Probably the most fascinating from a chemistry standpoint, Springerle come from the Swabian tradition of alkalized baking. Here I believe that our family recipe is actually MORE accurate than Dr. Oetker (essentially the German &amp;ldquo;Betty Crocker&amp;rdquo;), as Oetker recommends using their own branded &amp;ldquo;Backin&amp;rdquo; baking powder instead of Hirschhornsalz (Hartshorn, Ammonium Carbonate, Bakers Ammonium)
While obtaining Hartshorn used to be the most difficult part of making this recipe, it can now be easily obtained from Amazon.</description></item><item><title>Rezept: Spritzgebäck</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-24-rezept-spritzgeback/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-24-rezept-spritzgeback/</guid><description>Third up and most popular around Christmas at our house are Spritzgebäck&amp;hellip;. although they have always just been called &amp;ldquo;s-cookies&amp;rdquo; in our family.
American Recipe German Recipe (courtesy of Dr. Oetker) 2 1/2 cups (300g) Flour 1/2 tsp Salt 1 Cup (225g) Butter 3/4 Cup (150g) Sugar 1 Egg (or 3 Yolks) 3/4 tsp Almond Extract 500g (4.2 cups) Flour 1 pinch of Salt 250g (1.</description></item><item><title>Rezept: Zimtsterne</title><link>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-23-rezept-zimtsterne/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cambron.cc/recipes/2019-12-23-rezept-zimtsterne/</guid><description>Of particular interest to me, is the way in which immigrant foods, like Christmas cookies have changed to adapt to American tastes/American kitchens.
Having spent considerable time baking heirloom family cookie recipes in the kitchen at Christmas with my family. I thought it would be interesting to compare my family recipes with how they now exist in modern Germany.
My great aunt Alice was often considered the &amp;ldquo;master of these recipes&amp;rdquo; and helped translate some of them from German at sometime.</description></item></channel></rss>